I need to give this jumpsuit its own video and other jumpsuits too because you wanted to see it
you wanted to see more of it when I wore it for the hobble skirt video there were so many comments
about this jumpsuit so here we are I'm wearing it again I'm going to tell you more about it it's by
Bonafia a sportswear brand originally but yeah I can tell you I never wear these things for
working out but as fashion items it's an all-over print and I've seen a lot of
these kind of prints in the last few years and I can tell you this one is
very good so if I stretch it the print does not get white or lose its color and
on the inside it's completely purple so also nice color but you have this kind
of body contouring print here so the cat of the cat suit itself isn't even that special it's a
normal cut the special visual thing here is this like contouring we have darker areas at the edges
of the body and to contour muscles and a belly button and the lighter areas of course highlight
specific other parts it's the same as with makeup you highlight the i don't know the nose
or the chin if you want to draw attention to these parts. I've worn this for a full day on Malta when
I spend my holidays there because I love to wear these kind of active wear jumpsuits in the sun
because they block out the sun so I don't have to use sunscreen. And sweating is also no problem
because of the hydrophoric material. It helps the sweat to evaporate faster cooling you down.
it's very breathable and very very comfy so it's super comfy I can totally recommend it just as a
stylish studio outfit for example next up is this cut out thing suit here with a hole in the middle
and it's going to be looking all right I'd say this is more of a fashion jam suit
I would not wear it to work out to be honest because I think it's not supportive enough here
in this area but I think it's a great look we have removable pets in the bust
area so I can totally wear it without a bra I think bra would basically ruin the
look and it's very specific look I haven't seen a jumpsuit like this that
often that's why I wanted to try it the only thing you have to keep in mind
mind. While this one was completely opaque this one is slightly see-through. I noticed it also
on pictures so you can basically see my penny here and in the back. Of course you could wear
it without because you have the phone cut here made out of a different material but still we're
on YouTube better safe than sorry. You have the logo here and at the back and I also love the
lines here because they accentuate the bum and give it a nice little push-up lift and I do have
a discount code for Bonafide you get 30% off also if they have some sale action going on my discount
code stacks on top of that so you can get great bargains I will link everything down below and
now on to the next one this one's called techno wipe and I think it is definitely a wipe it's
jumpsuit again active wear fabric and I've seen a lot of printed catsuits they're usually very
plain in their cut but this one has a ton of features we have this body part so here's the
seam it goes in the back for this thong cut here again different panels we have a seam here in the
which is also of course a both sides which is also special so there's a lot
going on there is a lot of work that went into that a lot of panels I think
it's also on the arms are really long and the legs are really long which I
totally like and the pattern is also really cool it gives a kind of techno
cyber vibe besides the print and the cut we have another feature these yeah
sticky holographic prints here you can find it here I have one in the back here
very very visible so it's also kind of sticky if I touch it and also on the
leg and also here the Bonafide logo I think it's a great thing to add to this
catsuit because it gives it more dimension and I was like when I unpacked
oh this is so cool it also feels different it feels more like silicone I don't know
and it's very cool it adds to the color here and of course it works with my hair
the zipper hardware is made of metal and it features their signature logo which is a bum
of course I can open the zipper and there you see we have the signature band here which is
featured in a lot of their catsuits spelling their name I know a lot of people always call it
I don't like it it's too prominent it's too bold but yeah it's just their style it's their
signature look and I kind of like it because it adds another dimension to the look and if this
is too funky for you I'm going to show you a very classic black option last I'm going to admit it
this is one of my favorite Bonafido jumpsuits ever because I just love the look and it's super
comfy the fabric is so soft and smooth very stretchy very very comfy still active wear so
breathable perfect for a day in the city I did wear it on Malta too and I think it's very elegant
and with these lines you have here it looks so designerish there went a lot of thought into
the design we have this almost like a corset style look with the boning look alike I love it
also on the back side the v-shape and the bump shape here again the cut suit cut itself isn't
that fancy but these lines make it look 100 times more fancy or fancier so yeah of course
can close the zipper again but I prefer it open to be honest one thing I love about Bonafide is
also the length of the garments so these are not too short for me which is usually a problem with
my 173 centimeters. I really like their stuff and I'm really happy about the collaboration with them.
So if you want to try these garments yourself I can highly recommend them. Check out the discount
code in the description text. Check out my other Bonafido video on my channel here. I do have
pictures on Instagram and stuff as well so check out my socials and I will see you in the next video.
Have a nice day. Bye.